(Amy:)Penny's friend Zack stopped by
and said hello and I said "hoo."
(Raj:)Who?
(Penny:)Zack.
(Sheldon:)Then why did you ask?
(Amy:)Ask what?
Who.
(Penny:)Zack.
(Sheldon:)All right, let's start over.
(Sheldon:)What did you say
when Zack walked in?
"Hoo."
Zack.
Why do you keep saying "Zack"?
Because you keep saying "who."
I'm not saying "hoo" now.
I said "hoo" last night.
(Sheldon:)And the answer was Zack,
correct?
(Amy:)There was no question.
I simply said "hoo."
(Sheldon:)All right, I think
I have enough to go on.
(Sheldon:)Possible explanations
for your symptoms are,
(Sheldon:)in descending order
of likelihood:
(Sheldon:)hyperthyroidism,
premature menopause,
(Sheldon:)hosting an alien parasite or--
(Sheldon:)and I only include it
for the sake of covering
(Sheldon:)absolutely all bases--
sexual arousal.